<!--FILENAME-->
<!--DQC_0057-->
<!-- Copyright 2017 XBRL US Inc. All Rights Reserved. -->
<!-- Validation File Version 2.0 --><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="."?>
<testcase xmlns="http://xbrl.org/2008/conformance" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <creator>
    <name>Campbell Pryde</name>
    <email>campbell.pryde@xbrl.us</email>
  </creator>
  <number>DQC_0057</number>
  <ruleIdentifier>DQC_0057</ruleIdentifier>
  <description />
  <ruleMessage>One of the following elements ${elementNames.name} should appear as the opening and closing balance in the cash flow statement using the group ${nrole}.\nInstead the following balance items have been used in this statement ${balanceElements}. Depending if ASU-2016-18 has been adopted at least one of the opening and closing balance items listed must be used in the cash flow statement. \n \nRule version: ${ruleVersion}\n</ruleMessage>
  <variation id="DQC_0057.7494.8124">
    <name>Creates a fail case when an element in a predefined list does not appear as the opening and closing balance in the cash flow statement.</name>
    <description>Creates the following fail case: One of the following elements CashCashEquivalentsRestrictedCashAndRestrictedCashEquivalentsIncludingDisposalGroupAndDiscontinuedOperations, CashAndCashEquivalentsAtCarryingValue, Cash, CashAndCashEquivalentsAtCarryingValueIncludingDiscontinuedOperations, CashAndDueFromBanks, CashCashEquivalentsAndFederalFundsSold, CashEquivalentsAtCarryingValue, CashCashEquivalentsRestrictedCashAndRestrictedCashEquivalents should appear as the opening and closing balance in the cash flow statement using the group http://www.xxxx.com/role/StatementCONSOLIDATEDSTATEMENTSOFCASHFLOWS.\n Instead the following balance items have been used in this statement CashAndDueFromBanks1. Depending if ASU-2016-18 has been adopted at least one of the opening and closing balance items listed must be used in the cash flow statement.\n</description>
    <data>
      <schema>https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/763901/000119312517165435/0001193125-17-165435-xbrl.zip</schema>
      <instance readMeFirst="true">https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/763901/000119312517165435/0001193125-17-165435-xbrl.zip</instance>
    </data>
    <results blockedMessageCodes="DQC.US.0048.7482|DQC.US.0041.73">
      <error severity="error" count="1">DQC.US.0057.7494</error>
      <result>
        <primaryElement>ext:CashAndDueFromBanks1</primaryElement>
        <factValue>340225000</factValue>
        <endDate>2017-04-01</endDate>
        <dimensions />
        <unit>USD</unit>
        <message>One of the following elements ${elementNames.name} should appear as the opening and closing balance in the cash flow statement using the group ${nrole}.\nInstead the following balance items have been used in this statement ${balanceElements}. Depending if ASU-2016-18 has been adopted at least one of the opening and closing balance items listed must be used in the cash flow statement. \n \nRule version: ${ruleVersion}\n</message>
      </result>
    </results>
  </variation>
</testcase>
